bloggerspice.com 2018-03-23

# Privacy Policy - Blogger Spice

**Blogger Spice**  respects your privacy. At  **BloggerSpice**  we are conscious about your faith on us and our responsibility to protect your privacy. The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by **www.bloggerspice.com** and how it is used and how you can “opt-out”.

####  Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in different ways but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they willingly submit such information to us. Visitors can always refuse to provide personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

####  Log Files

**BloggerSpice**  makes use of log files through Google Analytic. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

####  How BloggerSpice use collected information

**BloggerSpice**  may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * To personalize your experience (Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To send periodic emails (The email address Users provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions)
  * To process transactions

####  How BloggerSpice protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

The email addresses collected via subscriptions to the  **BloggerSpice**  newsletters are not sold, or disclosed to any third parties. These addresses will only be used by our company to send out  **BloggerSpice**  communications (such as, the  **BloggerSpice**  newsletters, plug-in information and updates). You will not receive any mailings you did not request. The email addresses collected at  **BloggerSpice**  are stored on a secure dedicated server.

If you purchase products directly from  **BloggerSpice  **your contact information and a transaction history will be kept by Blogger Spice.  We may use the contact information to inform you about the status of your order, updates, bug fixes, and to let you know about upcoming  **BloggerSpice**  products.

Any data collected will be used by us.  **BloggerSpice**  hereby reserves the right to transfer any data collected in the event of an acquisition, full or partial, of the company or its assets.

####  BloggerSpice do not Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

####  Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on  **BloggerSpice**  that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

####  Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

####  Cookies and Web Beacons

**BloggerSpice**  does use cookies to store information about visitor’s preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

####  DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on  **BloggerSpice**.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to  **BloggerSpice**  and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - [Google Privacy & Terms](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on  **BloggerSpice**  send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

**BloggerSpice**  has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.  **BloggerSpice  **privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

####  Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit **http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.**

####  Changes to this privacy policy

**BloggerSpice**  has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

####  Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

####  Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please [contact us](http://www.bloggerspice.com/p/contact-admin.html)

This privacy policy was last updated on April[](http://www.blogger.com/blogger.g?blogID=6561335258261771689) 03, 2016
